

+46 768450055







in Linkedin

About me

I have a strong passion for game development, programming & games.

Skills

Programming Languages Game Engines

C#

Unity

C++

UE4

Java

Language

Source Tree Perforce

Swedish, native

Github Desktop Plastic SCM English

NIKLAS GRANSKOG

Programmer

Futuregames was an education that specialized in teaching students about the gaming industry. As for the programmer course, the focus was on C# & Unity with some courses in C++ & Unreal Engine 4.

I would describe myself as a person that wants to not only improve my skills, but use those skills to the best of my ability.

Work Experience

Gamucatex 2023-01-09 - Ongoing

Internship, Programmer C#, Unity

• Custom Console (Replacement for Unity's Console)

Landell Games AB 2022-06-20 - Ongoing Internship, Programmer C#, Unity

- Photon Networking
- Gameplay
- Damage System

Education

Rekt Games 2020

Internship, Gameplay Programmer C#, Unity

- Refactor similar gameplay elements with inheritance & polymorphism.
- Random Al movement for objects in the game scene.
- Simple UI transition between scenes.

Futuregames University

2018 - 2021

Gameplay programmer C#/C++

 Programmer for game projects in Unity and Unreal Engine 4.